Seirei Academy
Morning.
Morning!
Who is that? She's so pretty!
Check it out.
What? Whoa, it's Kujo-san.
Today's gonna be a good day.
Alisa Mikhailovna Kujo. Born to a Russian father.
Her grades are top of the school. She's also excellent at sports. Starting this year, she serves as the student council treasurer.
She's so dreamy.
Heya.
Morning, Kujo-san. And what
a pleasant morning it is, wouldn't you say?
Good morning.
It's our first time talking, I think?
I'm Ando, a second-year.
Your sister has told me lots about you,
and I've been wanting
to meet you because of it.
What do you say to having lunch together today?
No, thanks.
You drive a hard bargain. In that case,
could we exchange contact details at least?
I'm afraid I must refuse.
I have absolutely zero interest in you.
If that's all, I must be going now.
Oh, one last thing.
Your necklace is against school rules.
Whoa, she shot down Ando-senpai,
the most coveted guy in school, like nothing!
Talk about having high standards.
Kujo-san's here.
Morning, Kuze-kun.
Stayed up watching late-night anime again?
Oh, hey. Morning, Alya.
Yeah, something like that.
You never learn, do you?
You sacrifice sleep to watch your anime
and then snooze through school.
What's the point?
Hey, the anime finished airing at 1 AM.
The episode discussion took longer.
Discussion?
Oh, like on Twitter?
Nah. An otaku buddy and I
talked about it for two hours on a call.
Are you insane?
"Insane," eh? Let's think about it.
If professing my love for a particular work
with no regard for time or place
is the definition of insanity,
then I will gladly admit I am insane.
I take it back. You're just plain stupid.
I see you're in rare form today.
милашка.
What?
Uh, did you say something?
Nothing special.
I just said you look pathetic.
Well, excuse me.
Time
*School Store and Cafeteria open (12:30 - 13:20)
Short Homeroom & Cleaning
Monday
ENG Comm. I
Geography A
Intro Chem.
Math A
Art
Gen.
Tuesday
Intro Home Ec.
Phys. Ed.
Social Studies
Intro Phys.
JPN Gen.
Wednesday
Intro Chem
JPN Gen.
ENG Comm. I
Math I
ENG Expr. I
Long Homeroom
Thursday
Geography A
JPN Gen.
IT A
Phys Ed.
Friday
ENG Expr. I
Class Lit.
Phys Ed.
Math I
Intro Physics
Math A
Saturday
JPN Gen.
Math I
Art
Health & Phys.
Period
Homeroom
1st
2nd
3rd
4th
Lunch Break
5th
6th
HR & Cleaning
Huh?
What's wrong?
Oh, man.
Sorry, Alya, can I see your
chemistry workbook?
What, you forgot again?
Yeah, I probably left it at home.
Sure, I guess.
Thanks!
Iron. Cobalt.
Chromium
Manganese
Iron
Cobalt
What comes next?
Oh, do you know the answer, Kuze?
Huh? Uh...
Sorry about that.
Chromium
Manganese
Iron
Cobalt
If you know, then tell the class.
O-Okay.
Wait, what question are we even on?
Copper
It's 2! Copper!
Wrong.
Your turn, Kujo.
Yes, sir.
It's 8. Nickel.
Correct.
Try to pay attention in class, Kuze.
Yes, sir.
Manganese
Iron
Cobalt
Nickel
Don't just give me the wrong answer!
I was simply pointing out
which question we were on.
Yeah, right!
You were clearly pointing
at the second choice!
Lies and slander.
Try to be a little less obvious!
милашка.
What was that?
I called you stupid.
милашка.
You cutie, you.
What do you mean, cutie?!
You said that before, too!
I can understand you, you know!
Look at you. You're red as a baby.
Who're you calling a baby? You little...
Sometimes
in Russian
Hides Her
Feelings
Alya Sometimes Hides
Her Feelings in Russian
As a kid, I often played with a Russian girl
who lived near my grandpa's place.
Episode 1
Alya Hides Her Feelings in Russian
I must've picked it up then.
And I can still pretty much
understand spoken Russian.
But who woulda thought
it'd lead to this bizarre situation?
This cute Russian girl next to me fawns
over me exclusively in Russian, and I know!
If I came out and admitted it now...
Nope, not happening.
Outside of emergencies and cases
where they're needed for reference,
the use of mobile phones
is banned within school grounds.
Which means this is allowed,
because this is an emergency.
I'm going to ask you against
my better judgment: how, exactly?
Free rolls end in ten minutes.
You have some nerve, pulling this stunt
beside a student council officer.
Let's go! SSR Tsukuyomi is mine!
I'm taking that!
No!
Tsukuyomi? Like, the goddess
of the moon in Japanese mythology?
Why is her hair silver and not jet black?
Who knows? Probably a nod to the moon.
Who cares about that, anyway? She's cute.
You are too kind, milady!
Man, I really rolled Tsukuyomi-sama.
I have silver hair too, you know... You cheater.
Uh, what was that?
I called you a game junkie.
Hey, them's fighting words.
Wh-What?
You can't call me a junkie when I'm F2P.
That's an affront to
the true junkies: the P2W whales.
You make a good point. Nobody would
want to be put in the same category as you.
Savage!
And here I thought you actually looked
serious and committed for once.
Now, now. Commitment is my middle name,
and that's an understatement.
It's the overstatement of the century.
You do realize we have
another 80 years to go?
Gwargh! I wanna be a hit with the ladies!
What are you eating, Masachika?
Super spicy mapo ramen.
Hey! Don't ignore my soulful plea!
I figured it was
just the usual outburst.
Oh, great. Check out Mr. Hot Stuff over here.
Look, it's the student council!
Alisa Mikhailovna Kujo
Student Council Treasurer
We got here late. Are there any seats open?
Mariya Mikhailovna Kujo
Student Council Secretary
It's okay. I'll eat over there
with my classmates.
Suou Yuki
Student Council Spokesperson
Thank you for your
consideration, Masha-senpai.
The Kujo sisters are both so pretty.
Kujo-senpai is so pretty.
I'd love to get to know all about her.
I hear she's got a boyfriend, though.
Huh.
She keeps turning down boys who ask her out,
saying she's already dating someone.
Taken or not, Takeshi's still got no shot.
Shut it! Don't get a big head
just 'cause you're friends with Lady Alya!
Guh, I hate you.
How come you get to address
that ice queen with her nickname?
It's cool, I guess.
But she does keep snapping at me.
Hey, it's better than getting no response.
She basically never talks to anyone else.
Guess that's what sitting next to her
for more than a year gets you.
If I had to shoot my shot with one
of those three, it'd have to be Suou-san.
She's approachable, unlike Lady Alya,
so it feels like she's gettable!
Not that she isn't out of
most guys' league, of course.
Is she gettable, though? Apparently
she's turned down more guys than Kujo-san.
That's the problem.
She is a rich girl, so maybe she's
already been promised to someone?
You know anything, Masachika?
Why ask me?
Isn't that obvious?
May I sit here, Masachika-kun?
Sure, go ahead.
You guys okay with that?
Y-Y-Yeah.
Totally.
Thank you kindly.
I see you ordered
the same thing, Masachika-kun.
It's surprising that you have
a taste for that stuff too, Suou-san.
Oh, you needn't be so formal.
We're in the same year.
Well, if you say so.
And yes, of course I eat ramen.
I often go out to eat some on days off.
W-Wow.
This is lovely, though I do think
it could stand to be a bit spicier.
Right?
Wish we could top it with some chili oil.
It might be a good idea to
bring it up with the student council.
Don't bring your personal preferences
into admin matters.
I was simply joking.
Are you two friends?
We've known each other since we were kids.
You have?
Indeed. We've gone to school together
all the way from preschool to now.
Really?
Actually, are you two friends?
I suppose you could say it's a process.
If nothing else, I do want
to be friends with Alisa-san.
I don't think being friends
with me will be any fun.
So, you aren't entirely opposed to the idea?
I guess not.
Well, we're done here.
See you.
Okay?
They're too shiny for me. I can't!
By the way...
Masachika-kun, have you considered
my offer to join the student council?
Like I've said over and over,
I'm not interested.
I think you would be a great fit
with Alisa-san and myself.
And what's more,
you have experience as
student council vice president.
What?
When we were in middle school,
I was president and he was vice president.
Really?
I only ran because Yuki asked me to.
Elections at our school required
each candidate to have a running mate.
It may come as a surprise to you,
but he is capable of getting
things done, believe it or not.
Uh, "believe it or not"?
That's right.
You don't have to tell me. I know that already.
Oshiruko
So, you two are close, huh?
Surprised?
I very much am.
I never imagined that any girl
would want to be friends with you.
Huh? Excuse me?
What?
Uh, I just mean...
There's one right here?
Wait, are we friends?
Huh? Are we not?
No, you're right. We are friends.
Hey, where are you going?
I remembered something
I had to do at the student council office.
What's with her?
Hey!
Masachka!
Again, it's Masachika.
Hehe.
Come up here, Masachka!
Look at this beautiful sunset.
Yeah, it's very p... p...
Pretty.
Very pretty.
See you tomorrow, Masachka.
Yeah, see you.
I studied Russian like crazy
because I wanted to talk to her,
but I don't even remember her name.
Top of the morning to you!
Day Duty:
Kujo/Kuze
Perfect, if I do say so myself.
Hey, morning.
Morning, Kuze-kun.
I woke up real early this morning
and had nothing to do,
so I came in early and took care of some things.
You? Waking up early?
Hell must've frozen over.
You sure do know
how to pick the most biting remarks.
I'll wipe the blackboard in the morning.
Deal.
What happened there?
Did you step in a puddle or something?
No. I'm not like you.
Are you implying I'm a chronic spacer-outer?
Rest assured, I wasn't.
A truck splash-and-dashed me on the way here.
Oh, way to put a damper on things.
Well, it was partly my fault
for walking so close to the road.
And I have some spare socks, so I'll live.
Kuze-kun.
You were a student council officer
with Suou-san in middle school, right?
Hmm? Yeah, I was.
Huh.
Say, Kuze-kun.
Yeah?
Are you not willing to be
part of the student council?
Not you, too.
Answer me.
Yeah. I'm not interested in joining.
But what if I...
Nothing. Never mind.
Hey, could you grab a spare sock
for me from my locker?
Wha?
I can't go get it myself
now that I've taken it off.
Get to it.
Fine.
I'm opening it.
Here.
Put it on for me.
Wha?!
What's wrong?
Do you have to ask?
What's wrong with you?!
As thanks for grabbing my sock for me.
It would be a nice little treat for you, no?
That only holds true for a small set
of people with peculiar taste.
Oh, am I wrong?
Nope! Very much a treat!
It is for me, too.
Y'know, I've been wondering.
Why are her displays of affection
for me in Russian so weird?
Maybe her perfectionism in playing
her ideal self is stressing her out,
and she's using me as a release or something?
So she's mentally exposing herself...
Wait, she's an exhibitionist?
What?
Oh, just thinking about what you said.
Not much.
I just called you a coward.
Forget it. I'll put it on myself.
Nah, no need for that.
Hey, wait! Wh-What are you doing?!
What? Putting it on for you, as you requested.
I did, but...
You called me a coward,
and I'm not about to take that lying down.
Hey, wait! I'm...
I'm not ready for this!
H-Hey, stop squirming.
Easy for you to say!
Watch your hands!
Ow!
Ouch...
"Big news, sister of mine."
"What is it, beloved brother of mine?"
"
Stay calm and hear me out. I..."
"Gulp."
"I... may have a thing for legs."
"What... you say?!"
"I thought you were a
card-carrying member of
the planet of the baps!"
"As did I... Curses! Never did I think
I would fall prey to such proclivities!"
"Legs are lit. You go from the
plump thighs up top to the dainty
feet down below!"
"I know you'd get it, sister of mine."
As did I... Curses! Never did I think
I would fall prey to such proclivities!
Legs are lit. You go from the plump
thighs up top to the dainty feet down
below!
I knew you'd get it, sister of mine.
What is with this brain-dead convo?
Now, how do I solve the problem at hand?
Hey, Alya.
Alya!
What is it, Kuze-kun?
Hey, so, I just wanted to say...
You leg-fetishist perv.
Could you forgive me already?
Nah.
I'm not mad anymore.
And, uh, I'm sorry I kicked you.
Are you okay?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
I'm fine, I think.
Really?
You didn't hurt your neck or anything?
Nah, don't worry about it!
If anything, I should thank you for
giving me a peek into the promised land!
Huh?
Oops.
You got... a peek?
Wait, did you see my... p-pa...
Welp.
Thank you for the truly spectacular view!
I don't believe you! Die, stupid!
Hey, spare a thought for my neck!
Sorry! I took it a bit too far!
Shut up!
My bad!
Stop chasing me!
Let's talk this out!
There's nothing to talk about!
You sure do know
how to move, don't you?
10 Minutes Later
You okay there?
I would be, if you hadn't
chased me all over school.
Well, that's fair.
Anyway, you know...
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I get it, okay?
I'm not entirely blameless, either.
Milady, please accept this offering.
Oshiruko
What are you playing at?
I present this to thee
as a humble peace offering.
Drop the weird act.
I know you love your shiruko porridge.
You're always drinking it.
I'll take it. I just happen
to be thirsty.
True that.
Want a sip?
An indirect kiss scene out of nowhere?!
So, what, if I say yes here, we can get
some mouth-to-can-to-mouth action?!
Wh-What was that?
Chickened
out
I said, nothing beats a sweet drink
after a hard workout.
I think you meant to say "a cold drink."
He doesn't get any of this.
I heard what you said!